Campus Directories; Collection ua934
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Campus Directories Collection
1925-2006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany
ua934
2.06 cubic ft.
This collection is made up of directories to campus faculty and staff at the new York State College of Teachers and the University at Albany.
Administrative History
The New York State College for Teachers and the University at Albany provided contact information for faculty and staff by using campus directories. These directories were published yearly, as well as other version such as specific Summer session directories and one for specific departments. Publishing of these seems to have halted since the campus website provided all necessary contact information.
Scope and Contents
In this collection are the directories dating from 1925 to 2006. The majority are general directories to the faculty and staff, though some have a more specific target from certain departments, as well as seasonal copies such as the summer telephone directories. The information provided is the list of faculty and staff members working in all aspects of the University, as well as how they can be reached with information like office locations and telephone numbers.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized topically and chronolgoically within those groups.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Directories; Universities and colleges--Faculty; UAlbany Reference Collections
- New York State College Directory, 1925 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 1)
- New York State College Directory, 1926 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 2)
- New York State College Directory, 1927 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 3)
- New York State College Directory, 1928 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 4)
- New York State College Directory, 1929 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 5)
- New York State College Directory, 1930 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 6)
- New York State College Directory, 1931 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 7)
- New York State College Directory, 1932 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 8)
- New York State College Directory, 1933 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 9)
- New York State College Directory, 1934 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 10)
- New York State College Directory, 1935 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 11)
- New York State College Directory, 1936 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 12)
- New York State College Directory, 1937 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 13)
- New York State College Directory, 1938 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 14)
- New York State College Directory, 1939 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 15)
- New York State College Directory, 1940 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 16)
- New York State College Directory, 1941 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 17)
- New York State College Directory, 1942 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 18)
- New York State College Directory, 1943 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 19)
- New York State College Directory, 1944 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 20)
- New York State College Directory, 1945 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 21)
- New York State College Directory, 1946 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 22)
- New York State College Directory, 1947 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 23)
- New York State College Directory, 1948 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 24)
- New York State College Directory, 1949 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 25)
- New York State College Directory, 1950 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 26)
- New York State College Directory, 1951 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 27)
- New York State College Directory, 1952 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 28)
- New York State College Directory, 1953 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 29)
- New York State College Directory, 1954 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 30)
- New York State College Directory, 1955 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 31)
- New York State College Directory, 1956 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 32)
- New York State College Directory, 1957 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 33)
- New York State College Directory, 1958 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 34)
- New York State College Directory, 1959 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 35)
- University at Albany Directory, 1960 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 36)
- University at Albany Directory, 1961 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 37)
- University at Albany Directory, 1962 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 38)
- University at Albany Directory, 1963 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 39)
- University at Albany Directory, 1964 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 40)
- University at Albany Directory, 1965 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 41)
- Temporary Directory, 1966 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 42)
- University at Albany Directory, 1966 (Box 1 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 43)
- University at Albany Directory, 1967 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 1)
- University at Albany Directory, 1968 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 2)
- University at Albany Directory, 1969 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 3)
- University at Albany Directory, 1970 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 4)
- University at Albany Directory, 1971 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 5)
- University at Albany Directory, 1972 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 6)
- University at Albany Directory, 1973 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 7)
- University at Albany Directory, 1974 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 8)
- University at Albany Directory, 1975 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 9)
- University at Albany Directory, 1976 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 10)
- University at Albany Directory, 1977 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 11)
- University at Albany Directory, 1978 (Box 2 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 12)
- University at Albany Directory, 1979 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 1)
- University at Albany Directory, 1980 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 2)
- University at Albany Directory, 1981 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 3)
- University at Albany Directory, 1982 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 4)
- University at Albany Directory, 1983 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 5)
- University at Albany Directory, 1984 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 6)
- University at Albany Directory, 1985 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 7)
- University at Albany Directory, 1986 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 8)
- University at Albany Directory, 1987 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 9)
- University at Albany Directory, 1988 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 10)
- University at Albany Directory, 1989 (Box 3 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 11)
- University at Albany Directory, 1990 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 1)
- University at Albany Directory, 1991 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 2)
- University at Albany Directory, 1992 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 3)
- University at Albany Directory, 1993 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 4)
- University at Albany Directory, 1994 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 5)
- University at Albany Directory, 1995 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 6)
- University at Albany Directory, 1996 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 7)
- University at Albany Directory, 1997 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 8)
- University at Albany Directory, 1998 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 9)
- University at Albany Directory, 1999 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 10)
- University at Albany Directory, 2000 (Box 4 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 11)
- University at Albany Directory, 2001 (Box 5 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 1)
- University at Albany Directory, 2002 (Box 5 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 2)
- University at Albany Directory, 2003 (Box 5 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 3)
- University at Albany Directory, 2004 (Box 5 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 4)
- University at Albany Directory, 2005 (Box 5 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 5)
- University at Albany Directory, 2006 (Box 5 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 6)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1933 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 1)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1948 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 2)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1951 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 3)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1952 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 4)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1957 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 5)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1959 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 6)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1961 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 7)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1961 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 8)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1962 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 9)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1962 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 10)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1963 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 11)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1963 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 12)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1964 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 13)
- Directory Changes, 1964 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 14)
- Department of Germanic and Slavic Languages and Literature Directory, 1964 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 15)
- Summer Faculty Telephone Directory, 1964 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 16)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1965 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 17)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1966 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 18)
- Temporary Telephone Directory, 1966 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 19)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1967 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 20)
- Faculty Telephone Directory, 1972 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 21)
- Summer Session Telephone Directory, 1973 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 22)
- Summer Session Telephone Directory, 1974 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 23)
- Office Telephone Directories, 1965 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 24)
- Summer Telephone Directories, 1967 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 25)
- Office Telephone Directories, 1967 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 26)
- Summer Telephone Directories, 1968 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 27)
- Office Telephone Directories, 1968 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 28)
- Summer Telephone Directories, 1969 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 29)
- Office Telephone Directories, 1969 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 30)
- Office Telephone Directories, 1970 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 31)
- Summer Telephone Directories, 1971 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 32)
- Office Telephone Directories, 1971 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 33)
- State University of New York at Albany Directory Volume 1, 1985 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 34)
- State University of New York at Albany Directory Volume 2, 1985 (Box 6 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 35)
- A Great Place to Be, 1976 (Box 7 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 1)
- Resource Directory, 1991 (Box 7 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 2)
- Resource Directory, 1993 (Box 7 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 3)
- Resource Directory, 1994 (Box 7 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 4)
- Resource Directory, 1995 (Box 7 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 5)
- Resource Directory, 1996 (Box 7 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 6)
- Resource Directory, 1998 (Box 7 (Campus Directories Collection), Volume 7)